twestival.com 2015-04-29

# Twestival 2013: Privacy

**Last Updated:** 2 April 2013 

This Privacy Policy explains how information about you is collected, used, and disclosed by Connect the Dots Collective (doing business as and referred herein to as “Twestival”). This Privacy Policy applies to information Twestival collects when you use Twestival’s website and other online services (collectively, the “Services”), when you interact with Twestival on third-party sites where Twestival has an official presence, or when you otherwise interact with Twestival. 

Twestival may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. Upon making any changes, Twestival will notify you by revising the date at the top of this Privacy Policy and, in some cases, may provide you with additional notice, such as adding a statement to Twestival’s homepage or sending you an email notification. Twestival encourages you to review this Privacy Policy whenever you access the Services to stay informed about Twestival’s information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy. 

## Collection of Information

### Information You Provide to Twestival

Twestival collects information you directly provide. For example, Twestival collects information when you fill out a form, participate in any interactive features of the Services, sign up for Twestival’s newsletter, communicate with Twestival via third party social media sites, request support, or otherwise communicate with Twestival. The types of information Twestival may collect include your name, social networking screen name or ID, email address, city and country, and any other information you choose to provide. 

### Information Twestival Collects Automatically When You Use the Services

When you access or use the Services, Twestival automatically collects information about you, including: 

  * **Log Information:** Twestival logs information about your use of the Services, including the type of browser you use, access times, pages viewed, your IP address, and the page you visited before navigating to the Services.
  * **Device Information:** Twestival collects information about the device you use to access the Services, including the hardware model, operating system and version, and network information.
  * **Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies:** Twestival uses various technologies to collect information, and this may include sending cookies to your computer or mobile device. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory that help Twestival to improve the Services and your experience, see which areas and features of the Services are popular, and count visits. Twestival may also collect information using web beacons (also known as “tracking pixels”). Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in the Services or emails and help deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness, and determine whether an email has been opened and acted upon. For more information about cookies, and how to disable them, please see “Your Choices” below.

### Information Twestival Collects From Other Sources

Twestival may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information Twestival collects through the Services. For example, if you volunteer to organize or host an event, Twestival may collect information about you from publicly available sources and other third parties. 

## Use of Information

Twestival may use information about you for various purposes, including to: 

  * Provide, maintain, and improve the Services;
  * Communicate with you about volunteer opportunities, programs, trainings, events, donations, and other news and information Twestival thinks will be of interest to you;
  * Process your inquiries and respond to your comments, questions, and requests;
  * Monitor and analyze trends, usage, and activities in connection with the Services;
  * Link or combine with information Twestival gets from others to help understand your needs and provide you with better service; and
  * Carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected.

By accessing or using the Services or otherwise providing information to Twestival, you consent to the processing and transfer of information in and to the U.S. and other countries. 

## Sharing of Information

Twestival may share information about you as follows or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy: 

  * With organizers or hosts of Twestival events at which, or in locations where, you have indicated an interest in volunteering;
  * With vendors, consultants, and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work on Twestival’s behalf;
  * In response to a request for information if Twestival believes disclosure is in accordance with any applicable law, regulation, or legal process, or as otherwise required by any applicable law, rule, or regulation;
  * If Twestival believes your actions are inconsistent with the spirit or language of Twestival’s user agreements or policies, or to protect the rights, property, and safety of Twestival or others;
  * In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, reorganization, or acquisition of all or a portion of Twestival’s organization; and
  * With your consent or at your direction.

Twestival may also share aggregated or de-identified information, which cannot reasonably be used to identify you. 

## Social Sharing Features

The Services may offer social sharing features and other integrated tools (such as the Facebook “Like” button), that let you share actions you take on the Services with other media, and vice versa. The use of such features enables the sharing of information with your friends or the public, depending on the settings you establish with the entity that provides the social sharing feature. For more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and processing in connection with social sharing features, please visit the privacy policies of the entities that provide these features. 

## Analytics Services Provided by Others

Twestival may allow others to provide analytics services on Twestival’s behalf. These entities may use cookies, web beacons, and other technologies to collect information about your use of the Services and other websites, including your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked, and conversion information. Twestival and others may use this information to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, and better understand your online activity. 

## Security

Twestival takes reasonable measures to help protect information about you from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. 

## Your Choices

### Account Information

You may update, correct, or delete information about you at any time by emailing Twestival at [info@twestival.com](mailto:info@twestival.com). If you wish to deactivate your account, please email Twestival at [info@twestival.com](mailto:info@twestival.com), but note that Twestival may retain certain information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. Twestival may also retain cached or archived copies of information about you for a certain period. 

### Cookies

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Removing or rejecting browser cookies does not necessarily affect third party flash cookies used in connection with the Services. To delete or disable flash cookies please visit <https://www.adobe.com/security/flashplayer/> for more information. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of the Services. 

### Promotional Communications

You may opt out of receiving promotional communications from Twestival by following the instructions in those communications. If you opt out, Twestival may still send you non-promotional communications. 

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact Twestival at [info@twestival.com](mailto:info@twestival.com).
